zayconfoods.com 2017-07-02

# Zaycon Fresh - Privacy Policy

###    Zaycon Fresh 

Last updated March 10, 2015.

## Zaycon Privacy Statement

Zaycon Fresh, LLC is committed to protect your online privacy and believes it is important for you to know how we handle the information we receive from you via the internet.

Our Privacy Policy describes what information we collect online, how we protect it and what choices you have about how that information is used. We encourage you to read this Policy carefully so that you will understand the privacy standards used to ensure the security and confidentiality of your information. Should you have any questions about this policy or our privacy practices, please contact us in the following manner:

  1. Send an e-mail to Elizabeth Bartch at [ebartch@zayconfresh.com](mailto:ebartch@zayconfresh.com)
  2. Write to us at: Zaycon Fresh attn: Privacy Officer, 16201 E. Indiana Ste 2150, Spokane Valley, WA 99216

* * *

## What Personal Information Zaycon Collects

Zaycon will collect information that identifies you online only when you voluntarily provide it to us through our site when you register, place an order, or participate in our contests, surveys, sweepstakes, content submissions, and requests for suggestions. Depending on how you interact with us, this information may include your name, address, telephone number(s), email address and billing information.

We collect your email address and telephone number(s) so that we may communicate important information about your orders in real time. We maintain the data that you provide us, along with a record of your purchases, in a secure database.

To best serve you, we may combine this information with data that is publicly available and data that we receive from other reputable sources whose policies meet the Direct Marketing Association’s privacy standards.

* * *

## How Zaycon Protects the Security of Personal Information

Zaycon makes every reasonable effort to protect your personally identifiable information against unauthorized access or release and to ensure the security of transactions that occur on our site.

All the personal information you provide to us including payment information is handled through a Secure Socket Layer which is a leading Web technology that encrypts your account information.

Additionally, Zaycon maintains all personal customer data within the Zaycon information system firewalls that operate on separate Zaycon servers. The general public may not access these servers.

* * *

## Collection and Use of Non-Personal Information/Cookies

The Zaycon website uses technologies such as “cookies” and “pixel tags” (also known as “web beacons”) to identify which computer you are using, improve the functioning of our website and your experience.

Cookies are small data files that are automatically sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies enable us to remember what items are in your shopping cart, and to personalize your experience.

“Pixel tags” (or “web beacons”) are tiny graphical images embedded in webpages or emails. They are used to determine what parts of a website a visitor has viewed, or whether an email was successfully opened. These technologies do not contain any personal information about you; they are used to gather information to analyze traffic to the website, to improve our content and navigation, to enhance our marketing efforts, to personalize your experience, and to provide online display advertising tailored to your interests based on your online behavior.

You may prevent your computer from accepting cookies by modifying the properties on your web browser, however, stopping your computer from accepting cookies may limit your web browser’s functionality on the Zaycon website.

Zaycon also works with third-party marketing partners who use technologies such as cookies and pixel tags on our behalf. For details, see below.

* * *

## Third-Party Service Providers

Zaycon engages reputable third-party vendors to provide certain services such as drop-shipping, email distribution, market research, and third-party advertising. We provide these companies with only the information they need to perform their services and work closely with them to ensure that your privacy is respected and protected.

This includes third-party marketing partners who serve advertisements across the Internet on our behalf. They may use information about your visits to the website and other sites to deliver advertisements tailored to your interests. Although our website does not respond to a browser’s “Do Not Track” signal, you may opt-out of interest-based advertising.

To learn more about the use of this information and about advertising tailored to your interests by third parties, or to opt out, visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices> OR <http://www.aboutads.info/choices>.

If you opt-out, you will still receive advertisements, but they will not be delivered to you based upon your behavioral data possessed by the companies from whom you have opted-out. This process relies upon an opt-out cookie, so if you delete your cookies or _use a different computer, you will have to repeat this process_.

* * *

## Internet Links to Other Sites

As a convenience to our site visitors, Zaycon’s website may contain links to a number of sites that may provide useful information.

Links contained on the Zaycon website which transfer you to a non-Zaycon site are not maintained by Zaycon and may contain different information and/or different privacy policies from those of Zaycon. You may wish to review the privacy policies of these web sites and/or receive specific information regarding that site’s privacy policies and procedures after leaving Zaycon’s site.

Zaycon is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of a non-Zaycon website. Zaycon does not control, or have any input into, whether internet-linked sites use or accept cookies on their sites.

* * *

## Children’s Access

Zaycon is committed to the protection of children’s privacy, security, and safety. Our websites are created for an adult audience and are not designed or intended to attract children in any way. We do not knowingly solicit, collect or accept any information from children on this website.

* * *

## Email Communication

Zaycon sends email as necessary to site registrants and customers to respond to requests, facilitate order processing, or provide customer service. We may also send promotional emails about our products, special offers, events, or services. Email recipients may opt out at any time by following the “unsubscribe” instructions included in the email message or in the “My Account” section of our website.

* * *

## Changes to the Zaycon Privacy Policy

Zaycon may alter or make changes to this privacy policy from time to time when developments occur and/or technology improvements are implemented. When changes are made, we will update our privacy policy and notices. Please review this page periodically to ensure that you are aware of any such updates.

* * *

## Your Consent

By visiting and using Zaycon’s website and the contents therein, you consent to the collection, use and disclosure of information as described in this policy.
